[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "How are you both?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "both", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Very good.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Do you feel like you've been to the lion's den a bit tonight?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "like", "you", "'ve", "been", "to", "the", "lion", "'s", "den", "a", "bit", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "A little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "I always get nervous in interviews, especially being on CNN.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "always", "get", "nervous", "in", "interviews", ",", "especially", "being", "on", "CNN", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Why CNN?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "CNN", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Because it's just, you know, a very serious place and you make me nervous.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "'s", "just", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "very", "serious", "place", "and", "you", "make", "me", "nervous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Would you like to be taken more seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "be", "taken", "more", "seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RBR", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "I would.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Why would you care about being taken seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "care", "about", "being", "taken", "seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Because I feel like I've really grown in the past couple of years, I just turned 30, I'm an adult, and I feel that I deserve it.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "feel", "like", "I", "'ve", "really", "grown", "in", "the", "past", "couple", "of", "years", ",", "I", "just", "turned", "30", ",", "I", "'m", "an", "adult", ",", "and", "I", "feel", "that", "I", "deserve", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "How did it make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "it", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "It was exciting.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "exciting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Are you saying Paris is shy?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "saying", "Paris", "is", "shy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "She can be.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "can", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Paris"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "You can be shy?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "be", "shy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "What place do you need to be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "place", "do", "you", "need", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Because I missed you.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "missed", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Paris"]}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "What are you promoting?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "promoting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "I'm here for \"The World According To Paris,\" which is my new TV show.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "here", "for", "``", "The", "World", "According", "To", "Paris", ",", "''", "which", "is", "my", "new", "TV", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "How interested are you in the world?", "question_tokens": ["How", "interested", "are", "you", "in", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Very.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Are you interested in world affairs?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "interested", "in", "world", "affairs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Genuinely?", "question_tokens": ["Genuinely", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "When you see what's going on in the Middle East and stuff like that, do you have a -- do you have a healthy interest or does that kind of stuff not really touch your life?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "and", "stuff", "like", "that", ",", "do", "you", "have", "a", "--", "do", "you", "have", "a", "healthy", "interest", "or", "does", "that", "kind", "of", "stuff", "not", "really", "touch", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, I have so much going on in my life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "so", "much", "going", "on", "in", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "What's it like being Paris Hilton's mom?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "it", "like", "being", "Paris", "Hilton", "'s", "mom", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "It's been quite an experience.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "quite", "an", "experience", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Paris Hilton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Are you happy with that relationship with the media?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "happy", "with", "that", "relationship", "with", "the", "media", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "You know, it used to really bother me when I first came out in the media when I was 15 years old.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "used", "to", "really", "bother", "me", "when", "I", "first", "came", "out", "in", "the", "media", "when", "I", "was", "15", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Do you Google yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "Google", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Not really.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Google"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "If you -- if you came on \"America's Got Talent,\" what would your -- what would your talent be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "--", "if", "you", "came", "on", "``", "America", "'s", "Got", "Talent", ",", "''", "what", "would", "your", "--", "what", "would", "your", "talent", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "WP", "MD", "VB", ":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Singing.", "answer_tokens": ["Singing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Are you getting you're a serious singer or are you a brand singer, as an extension of your brand?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "getting", "you", "'re", "a", "serious", "singer", "or", "are", "you", "a", "brand", "singer", ",", "as", "an", "extension", "of", "your", "brand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "It's just part of my brand.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "part", "of", "my", "brand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "I mean, Kathy, what do you think of modern fame in that sense, that you can actually see your daughter, Paris, not going through a conventional talent like acting or any of those kind of things, but just being Paris Hilton and making all this money?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "Kathy", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "modern", "fame", "in", "that", "sense", ",", "that", "you", "can", "actually", "see", "your", "daughter", ",", "Paris", ",", "not", "going", "through", "a", "conventional", "talent", "like", "acting", "or", "any", "of", "those", "kind", "of", "things", ",", "but", "just", "being", "Paris", "Hilton", "and", "making", "all", "this", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathy"], "LOCATION": ["Paris", "Paris Hilton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Do you worry about her?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "worry", "about", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "I used to but I really don't as much anymore.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "used", "to", "but", "I", "really", "do", "n't", "as", "much", "anymore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Because she's behaving better?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "she", "'s", "behaving", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "She's behaving better and she's grown up and she's been through a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "behaving", "better", "and", "she", "'s", "grown", "up", "and", "she", "'s", "been", "through", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "But you're aware you become an adult at 18?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "'re", "aware", "you", "become", "an", "adult", "at", "18", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Why are people so fascinated by Paris, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "people", "so", "fascinated", "by", "Paris", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "I think that, you know, she has a famous last name.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "she", "has", "a", "famous", "last", "name", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Paris"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "And a lot of people look at her and say, well, why does she have to go and do anything?", "question_tokens": ["And", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "look", "at", "her", "and", "say", ",", "well", ",", "why", "does", "she", "have", "to", "go", "and", "do", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "She didn't have to.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "did", "n't", "have", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Is this show that we're now going to see more of the real Paris do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "show", "that", "we", "'re", "now", "going", "to", "see", "more", "of", "the", "real", "Paris", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "This show is all real, everything that happens and it was like I was finally ready to show who I really was and I'm really honest in the show.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "show", "is", "all", "real", ",", "everything", "that", "happens", "and", "it", "was", "like", "I", "was", "finally", "ready", "to", "show", "who", "I", "really", "was", "and", "I", "'m", "really", "honest", "in", "the", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Paris"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hilton"]}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "What are the misconceptions about you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "misconceptions", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Oh, I think there's definitely a lot, just having the last name Hilton, people assume that everything was handed to me and I've never had to work a day in my life.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "definitely", "a", "lot", ",", "just", "having", "the", "last", "name", "Hilton", ",", "people", "assume", "that", "everything", "was", "handed", "to", "me", "and", "I", "'ve", "never", "had", "to", "work", "a", "day", "in", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "RP", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "How much of that goes down to your parents?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "that", "goes", "down", "to", "your", "parents", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Just growing up my parents never spoiled us.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "growing", "up", "my", "parents", "never", "spoiled", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Family?", "question_tokens": ["Family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Family.", "answer_tokens": ["Family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "How did you actually feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "actually", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "I was in shock.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "in", "shock", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Did you call your mum?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "call", "your", "mum", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Do you remember, Kathy?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", ",", "Kathy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "You know, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "How did you get her back on track?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "get", "her", "back", "on", "track", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "We had therapy and I think that that really helped.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "therapy", "and", "I", "think", "that", "that", "really", "helped", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "What can you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "I didn't know what to say.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "know", "what", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "What do you feel about them now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "them", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "I just -- just felt so betrayed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "--", "just", "felt", "so", "betrayed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "That you loved?", "question_tokens": ["That", "you", "loved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "I thought I did and I can't believe that he would do something like that to me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "I", "did", "and", "I", "ca", "n't", "believe", "that", "he", "would", "do", "something", "like", "that", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Do you have a tissue?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "tissue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Do you want to take a little break?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "take", "a", "little", "break", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "No, it's OK, just --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "OK", ",", "just", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "When this whole tape thing blew up, what did Donald Trump say to you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "this", "whole", "tape", "thing", "blew", "up", ",", "what", "did", "Donald", "Trump", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "He was furious.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "furious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Did he give any advice on how to deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "give", "any", "advice", "on", "how", "to", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Dad and I talked with him mostly.", "answer_tokens": ["Dad", "and", "I", "talked", "with", "him", "mostly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["this for 15 years"]}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "PDT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "What do you think of the whole fame game now that you've had enough time to be in it for a while?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "whole", "fame", "game", "now", "that", "you", "'ve", "had", "enough", "time", "to", "be", "in", "it", "for", "a", "while", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Well, I've been doing this for 15 years now, so half of my life and there's it's up and downs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "doing", "this", "for", "15", "years", "now", ",", "so", "half", "of", "my", "life", "and", "there", "'s", "it", "'s", "up", "and", "downs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "What are those things that you wish you didn't have to put up with, other than what we've just discussed?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "those", "things", "that", "you", "wish", "you", "did", "n't", "have", "to", "put", "up", "with", ",", "other", "than", "what", "we", "'ve", "just", "discussed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "One of the things is in the media, there's all these people who I've never met before, or maybe people from my past who want to sell stories and make money, so they'll make up these crazy stories and people believe them.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "things", "is", "in", "the", "media", ",", "there", "'s", "all", "these", "people", "who", "I", "'ve", "never", "met", "before", ",", "or", "maybe", "people", "from", "my", "past", "who", "want", "to", "sell", "stories", "and", "make", "money", ",", "so", "they", "'ll", "make", "up", "these", "crazy", "stories", "and", "people", "believe", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Are you really entitled to any privacy given the amount of your private life that you put out there for commercial gain?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "really", "entitled", "to", "any", "privacy", "given", "the", "amount", "of", "your", "private", "life", "that", "you", "put", "out", "there", "for", "commercial", "gain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Well, when you're in this business, this is what you sign up for.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "you", "'re", "in", "this", "business", ",", "this", "is", "what", "you", "sign", "up", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Is that a price worth paying, in the end?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "price", "worth", "paying", ",", "in", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "Sometimes.", "answer_tokens": ["Sometimes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Did you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "She was a tomboy.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "was", "a", "tomboy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "What do you think is behind that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "is", "behind", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "I think it has a lot to do with your family.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "has", "a", "lot", "to", "do", "with", "your", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Do you think you were?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "were", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Deliberately, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Deliberately", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Well, it was my first child, and I thought this is, you know, my little China cup.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "my", "first", "child", ",", "and", "I", "thought", "this", "is", ",", "you", "know", ",", "my", "little", "China", "cup", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "VBG", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "JJ", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What were the misconceptions about Michael, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "the", "misconceptions", "about", "Michael", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Well, there was not a kinder, more generous, loving, sweet, smart, smart -- I can't -- the most wonderful father.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "was", "not", "a", "kinder", ",", "more", "generous", ",", "loving", ",", "sweet", ",", "smart", ",", "smart", "--", "I", "ca", "n't", "--", "the", "most", "wonderful", "father", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Where were you when you heard he died?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "you", "heard", "he", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "I had just come back to the hotel.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "just", "come", "back", "to", "the", "hotel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "How did you hear the news?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "hear", "the", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "My assistant told me.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "assistant", "told", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Jackson"]}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What was the scene there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "scene", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "The children and Mrs. Jackson and all the brothers and sisters and just everybody was in this room.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "children", "and", "Mrs.", "Jackson", "and", "all", "the", "brothers", "and", "sisters", "and", "just", "everybody", "was", "in", "this", "room", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Did you say anything?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "say", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "What did you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Incredibly sad end to his life, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Incredibly", "sad", "end", "to", "his", "life", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "And he was so fabulous at the hotel.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "he", "was", "so", "fabulous", "at", "the", "hotel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ":", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Paris, did you know Michael well?", "question_tokens": ["Paris", ",", "did", "you", "know", "Michael", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Yeah, I grew up -- just my mom -- I remember -- one of the first memories I have of him was when my mom took us to the music video set of \"Thriller.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "grew", "up", "--", "just", "my", "mom", "--", "I", "remember", "--", "one", "of", "the", "first", "memories", "I", "have", "of", "him", "was", "when", "my", "mom", "took", "us", "to", "the", "music", "video", "set", "of", "``", "Thriller", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"], "LOCATION": ["Paris"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I was honored.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "honored", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Latoya"]}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Was it a direct result?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "a", "direct", "result", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "You know, Latoya will tell you the story.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Latoya", "will", "tell", "you", "the", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Have you seen the children much since he died?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "seen", "the", "children", "much", "since", "he", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I saw them a couple weeks ago.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "saw", "them", "a", "couple", "weeks", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Bel Air Hotel"]}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "NN", ":", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Is that an inaccurate portrayal, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "an", "inaccurate", "portrayal", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Well, I can tell you that when he was at the Bel Air Hotel, there was none -- there was none of that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "that", "when", "he", "was", "at", "the", "Bel", "Air", "Hotel", ",", "there", "was", "none", "--", "there", "was", "none", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "What do you think his legacy will be, Michael Jackson?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "his", "legacy", "will", "be", ",", "Michael", "Jackson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Well, I think that now that he's gone, everybody realizes what a good person, all the wonderful things that he's done for charity.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "now", "that", "he", "'s", "gone", ",", "everybody", "realizes", "what", "a", "good", "person", ",", "all", "the", "wonderful", "things", "that", "he", "'s", "done", "for", "charity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "How many current businesses do you have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "current", "businesses", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I have 17 different product lines.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "17", "different", "product", "lines", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Do you keep a handle on it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "keep", "a", "handle", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I don't think you know that part.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "know", "that", "part", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "I would imagine it's more than that, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "would", "imagine", "it", "'s", "more", "than", "that", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Is it a lot more?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "lot", "more", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I do very well for myself.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "very", "well", "for", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "If you were pitching it to me, what do you personify?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "pitching", "it", "to", "me", ",", "what", "do", "you", "personify", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "Fashion, fun, excitement, and amazing products.", "answer_tokens": ["Fashion", ",", "fun", ",", "excitement", ",", "and", "amazing", "products", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Do you keep a close eye on the money?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "keep", "a", "close", "eye", "on", "the", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "That I bet she does.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "I", "bet", "she", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 606, "question": "You do?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Don't to every what's this -- what's this --", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "to", "every", "what", "'s", "this", "--", "what", "'s", "this", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "How do you trust men?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "trust", "men", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "It's about someone who has their own thing going on.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "about", "someone", "who", "has", "their", "own", "thing", "going", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "You've been with him a couple years?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "been", "with", "him", "a", "couple", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "Over a year now.", "answer_tokens": ["Over", "a", "year", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Is this true love?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "true", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "I've never been happier.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "never", "been", "happier", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "Think we may be seeing some real wedding bells soon?", "question_tokens": ["Think", "we", "may", "be", "seeing", "some", "real", "wedding", "bells", "soon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "We'll see what happens.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ll", "see", "what", "happens", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Could you imagine being 35 and not married?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "imagine", "being", "35", "and", "not", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "CD", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "You know, I would love to have a family and children in the next couple of years, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "would", "love", "to", "have", "a", "family", "and", "children", "in", "the", "next", "couple", "of", "years", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "Do you think he's the one?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "the", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "Paris, what 37,000 things are you up to?", "question_tokens": ["Paris", ",", "what", "37,000", "things", "are", "you", "up", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Paris"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Where?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "Around the world.", "answer_tokens": ["Around", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald"]}, "docId": "110605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Is that the game plan?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "game", "plan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "I think Donald is a brand.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Donald", "is", "a", "brand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]